export const questions:Question[] = [
    {
        id:'1',
        type:'radio',
        score:2,
        question: "What is the name of the project?",
        answers:['new','test','with','out']
    },{
        id:'2',
        type:'checkbox',
        score:2,
        question: "你喜欢哪个明星",
        answers:['百里守约','刘玥','张本智和','张继科','苍井空']
    },{
        id:'3',
        type:'judge',
        score:2,
        question: "What is the name of the project?",
        answers:['对','错']
    },{
        id:'4',
        type:'blank',
        score:2,
        question: "What is the name of the project?",
        answers:["",""]
    },
    {
        id:'5',
        type:'radio',
        score:2,
        question: "What is the name of the project?",
        answers:['new','test','with','out']
    },{
        id:'6',
        type:'checkbox',
        score:2,
        question: "你喜欢哪个明星",
        answers:['百里守约','刘玥','张本智和','张继科','苍井空']
    },{
        id:'7',
        type:'judge',
        score:2,
        question: "What is the name of the project?",
        answers:['对','错']
    },{
        id:'8',
        type:'blank',
        score:2,
        question: "What is the name of the project?",
        answers:["",""]
    },{
        id:'9',
        type:'judge',
        score:2,
        question: "What is the name of the project?",
        answers:['对','错']
    },{
        id:'10',
        type:'blank',
        score:2,
        question: "What is the name of the project?",
        answers:["",""]
    }



]



